Geetha Sidhambaram

▼ TW9 2JR, Richmond, London 🔀 sidh.geetha@gmail.com 📞 07438623564 🔉 Female

■ Indian, eligible to work in the UK

Profile

Have 4 years of experience in auditing projects, managing internal audits, supporting teams during external audits, monitoring non-compliance statuses, and maintaining organized documentation using an efficient internal tracking tool. Additionally, actively contributed as part of the agile process across various project teams.

I am seeking an opportunity to reinvigorate my career path after my break, and I am eager to prove my skills and contribute effectively.

Education

Bachelor of Science, Bharathiar University

Master of Science in Computer Science, Bharathiar University

Diploma in fine arts, Rockstartists Studio 2

UXUI Design, Buff Creative College Chennai 🛭

Full stack development,

GUVI GEEK NETWORK PRIVATE LIMITED 173

2007 - 2010 | Tamilnadu, India

2010 - 2012 | Tamilnadu, India

2022 - 2022 | Delhi, India

06/2019 - 10/2021 | Chennai, India

12/2023 - 12/2024 | Chennai, India

Skills

Figma

Invision

User Research

Prototyping

Competitor analysis

Information architecture

Github

CSS Frameworks

Tailwind CSS **Bootstrap** ChakraUI

Balsamiq

SDLC

Agile Methodologies

Wireframing

Wireframe

Responsive Design

UI Design

Front end

- HTML, CSS, javascript, React is
- Mongodb, PostgresSQL
- API, Postman
- Github

Work Experience

UI/UX Designer, Freelancer (Beginner)

https://www.behance.net/geethas ♂

04/2021 - present | London, India

ALTR - Community-based goal settings mobile app. ALTR is designed to help anyone to achieve their goals for selfimprovement.

VilFresh - Redesigned e-commerce app that aims to bring village fresh products to urban citizens. The Vilfresh app allows you to buy a village fresh products like milk, fruits, and grocery items that come directly from the farmers. **M2M Builders** - Website design for building construction company.

Home Maker, Family

2016 - 2020 | Bangalore, India

- Learned programming skills like HTML and CSS.
- Completed diploma in Fine Arts course.
- Leading children in activities by reading stories, doing crafts, and helping to build social skills.

• Planned, assisted families, prepared nutritious meals.

Senior Quality Analyst, Infosys Ltd.

05/2013 - 03/2017 | Bangalore, India

- Audited projects based on the SDLC process and raising NC's if there are any deviations.
- Assisted with corrective action plans and monitored status project status, tracked NC's to Closure with RCA & CAPA.
- Audited code releases and artifacts.
- Guided various projects during external audits AT 801(SSAE).
- Conducted the change management audit and implemented it in a controlled manner.